vidohe.com 2011-06-02

# DownloadHelper - Media download Firefox extension

## Web hosts

As you can see navigating our site, the displayed hostname in the url may change between _www.downloadhelper.net_ and _www.vidohe.com_. This is only for technical reasons, and both domains are hosted from the same servers, using the same technology. We name the whole site, whatever its domain, _downloadhelper.net_.

## Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site uses a few cookies for statistical purpose. In particular a cookie may be set by the extension to export the number of downloads you performed using Video DownloadHelper. If this is a problem for you, you can very easily disable the use of this cookie from the extension preferences. In no way, can those cookies be used to track your online activities.

As with most web sites, some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). If you are converned about this, we recommend you disable third-party cookies from your browser's preferences (Note that we have no access to or control over these cookies).

## Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with ad companies: Google Adsense, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

## Site navigation analyzing

As many web sites around, we use Google Analytics to collect anonymously information about your navigation on our site. We analyze this information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. downloadhelper.net may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of the downloadhelper.net search and navigation.

## Personal information

Should you contact us for technical support, partnership request or any other reason, we will communicate through email. Your email address will not be disclosed, given or sold to anyone, including third-party partners.

In the case of a technical support mail exchange, we may publish the content of the mail thread (without personal information like email or IP address) to our knowledge base as this may be an efficient source of information for the other users.

## Changes to privacy policy

We reserve the right to amend or revise this privacy policy from time to time. We will post these changes to this page. Use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used.
